

# Saku Hellström

**IT-BUSINESS STUDENT** 

# **PROFILE**

I am a final year IT-Business student. I don't have any work experience from IT yet, but in my studies I've used many different technologies and programming languages. I am a very adaptive person and I get along with all kinds of people.

### CONTACT

- +358 44 0377 100
- saku.hellstrom@gmail.com
- Ainonkatu 4-6 B 23 40100 Jyväskylä

### SKILLS/COURSES

- HTML/CSS
- Javascript, React, Node.js
- SQL, PostGreSQL
- Python
- C#
- PHP/Laravel
- Windows, MacOS, Linux
- Microsoft Azure Fundamentals

#### LANGUAGES

Finnish NativeEnglish FluentSwedish Basics

# REFERENCES

- Jukka Moilanen, Posti Group Oyj, Lappeenranta
- Contact information upon request

#### **EDUCATION**



LAB University of Applied Sciences

8/2020 - 12/2024

# Bachelor's Degree Programme in Business Information Technology

- I will graduate as a bachelor of Business IT at the end of this year.
- So far I've got 165 credits and have a GPA of 3,59



Savitaipaleen lukio

2015 - 2018

High School Diploma

- I graduated from high school in 2018.
- Diploma GPA was 7,8

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**



Posti Group Oyj

8/2018 - 8/2022

# Postal Service Worker

I worked as a postal service worker before serving in the military from 8/18 to 12/18, and after the service from 1/20 to 8/20. I've also worked summer jobs ther in 2021 and 2022.

My job included:

- Sorting mail
- · Delivering mail and packages
- Customer service related to the job



Other summer jobs

2015 - 2018

# Savitaipaleen Kotiseutuyhdistys, Savitaipaleen Nuorison tuki Ry, Saimaan Kuitu Oy

I've also had many different summer jobs before working at Posti. For example as a guide for a local open-air museum, customer service for an ISP and also gardening jobs like lawn mowing etc.